{
  "text_qualification": "We have assessed these for investments not within superannuation. To see within superannuation",
  "text_answer_heading": "Based on your answers, the following providers may be suitable: ",
  "notification": "Click the structure/provider above to see why it is/is not suitable",
  "categories": [
    {
      "name": "21st Century Structures",
      "subcategories": [
        {
          "name": "Nucleus Wealth",
          "id": 1,
          "suitability": "YES",
          "reasons": [
            {
              "question_id": 1,
              "question_text": "How much do you know about investing",
              "answer_id": 3,
              "answer_text": "I don't have any experience",
              "reason_text": "Some text to explain why suitable/not suitable"
            },
            {
              "question_id": 2,
              "question_text": "How much control do you want over your asset allocation (i.e. whether the underlying investments are in stocks or bonds or other investments)?",
              "answer_id": 3,
              "answer_text": "I want to help choose the investment manager/product, but then I don't mind not having control",
              "reason_text": "Some text to explain why suitable/not suitable"
            },
            {
              "question_id": 1,
              "question_text": "How much do you know about investing",
              "answer_id": 3,
              "answer_text": "I don't have any experience",
              "reason_text": "Some text to explain why suitable/not suitable"
            },
            {
              "question_id": 2,
              "question_text": "How much control do you want over your asset allocation (i.e. whether the underlying investments are in stocks or bonds or other investments)?",
              "answer_id": 3,
              "answer_text": "I want to help choose the investment manager/product, but then I don't mind not having control",
              "reason_text": "Some text to explain why suitable/not suitable"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "name": "Online Broker",
          "id": 2,
          "suitability": "NO",
          "reasons": [
            {
              "question_id": 1,
              "question_text": "How much do you know about investing",
              "answer_id": 3,
              "answer_text": "I have alot of experience",
              "reason_text": "Some text to explain why suitable/not suitable"
            },
            {
              "question_id": 2,
              "question_text": "How much control do you want over your asset allocation (i.e. whether the underlying investments are in stocks or bonds or other investments)?",
              "answer_id": 3,
              "answer_text": "I want to help choose the investment manager/product, but then I don't mind not having control",
              "reason_text": "Some text to explain why suitable/not suitable"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "name": "Robo Advise",
          "id": 3,
          "suitability": "UNSURE",
          "reasons": [
            {
              "question_id": 1,
              "question_text": "How much do you know about investing",
              "answer_id": 3,
              "answer_text": "I have an average amount of experience",
              "reason_text": "Some text to explain why suitable/not suitable"
            },
            {
              "question_id": 2,
              "question_text": "How much control do you want over your asset allocation (i.e. whether the underlying investments are in stocks or bonds or other investments)?",
              "answer_id": 3,
              "answer_text": "I want to help choose the investment manager/product, but then I don't mind not having control",
              "reason_text": "Some text to explain why suitable/not suitable"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "name": "Traditional Structures",
      "subcategories": [
        {
          "name": "Stock Broker",
          "id": 4,
          "suitability": "YES",
          "reasons": [
            {
              "question_id": 1,
              "question_text": "How much do you know about investing",
              "answer_id": 3,
              "answer_text": "I have an average amount of experience",
              "reason_text": "Some text to explain why suitable/not suitable"
            },
            {
              "question_id": 2,
              "question_text": "How much control do you want over your asset allocation (i.e. whether the underlying investments are in stocks or bonds or other investments)?",
              "answer_id": 3,
              "answer_text": "I want to help choose the investment manager/product, but then I don't mind not having control",
              "reason_text": "Some text to explain why suitable/not suitable"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "name": "Financial Planner",
          "id": 5,
          "suitability": "NO",
          "reasons": [
            {
              "question_id": 1,
              "question_text": "How much do you know about investing",
              "answer_id": 3,
              "answer_text": "I have an average amount of experience",
              "reason_text": "Some text to explain why suitable/not suitable"
            },
            {
              "question_id": 2,
              "question_text": "How much control do you want over your asset allocation (i.e. whether the underlying investments are in stocks or bonds or other investments)?",
              "answer_id": 3,
              "answer_text": "I want to help choose the investment manager/product, but then I don't mind not having control",
              "reason_text": "Some text to explain why suitable/not suitable"
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "name": "Managed Funds/Listed Invest. Companies",
          "id": 6,
          "suitability": "NO",
          "reasons": [
            {
              "question_id": 1,
              "question_text": "How much do you know about investing",
              "answer_id": 3,
              "answer_text": "I have an average amount of experience",
              "reason_text": "Some text to explain why suitable/not suitable"
            },
            {
              "question_id": 2,
              "question_text": "How much control do you want over your asset allocation (i.e. whether the underlying investments are in stocks or bonds or other investments)?",
              "answer_id": 3,
              "answer_text": "I want to help choose the investment manager/product, but then I don't mind not having control",
              "reason_text": "Some text to explain why suitable/not suitable"
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
